(Howard:)Can't you face the other way and listen?
(Raj:)I can't do anything right for you, can I?
(Howard:)What the hell is he up to?
(Raj:)He is kind of a weirdo.
(Raj:)Maybe he's got Leonard Nimoy
chained up in there.
(Raj:)Or Bill Gates. Or Stephen Hawking.
(Howard:)Why would he chain up Stephen Hawking?
Howard, you can't treat the man differently
just because he's disabled. That's not okay.
(Leonard:)If you're wondering why I've been staring...
(Leonard:)...I'm trying to get a look at this guy
who's coming over to Penny's.
(Sheldon:)To be honest, I didn't know you were here.
(Leonard:)It's not a big deal.
He's just in her history class.
(Leonard:)They're working on a project.
I don't even know why I care.
(Leonard:)- You know what, I don't care.
- You think you don't care.
(Leonard:)This is silly. I have nothing to worry about.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I don't know.